James Kolbe Papers, 1958-2006 (bulk 1985-2006)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 2: Congressional Activities, 1980-2006
  - Series 6: Correspondence, 1983-2006
    - Acknowledgements and Requests, 1983-2006
      - Kudos (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 161, Folder 17)
      - Kudos (2 of 2), 1993 (Box 161, Folder 18)
      - Kudos (1 of 3), 1994 (Box 161, Folder 19)
      - Kudos (2 of 3), 1994 (Box 161, Folder 20)
      - Kudos (3 of 3), 1994 (Box 161, Folder 21)
      - Kudos (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 161, Folder 22)
      - Kudos (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 161, Folder 23)
      - Kudos (1 of 3), 1996 (Box 162, Folder 1)
      - Kudos (2 of 3), 1996 (Box 162, Folder 2)
      - Kudos (3 of 3), 1996 (Box 162, Folder 3)
      - Kudos, 1997 (Box 162, Folder 4)
      - Kudos (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 162, Folder 5)
      - Kudos (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 162, Folder 6)
      - Kudos (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 162, Folder 7)
      - Kudos (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 162, Folder 8)
      - Kudos (1 of 3), 2000 (Box 162, Folder 9)
      - Kudos (2 of 3), 2000 (Box 162, Folder 10)
      - Kudos (3 of 3), 2000 (Box 162, Folder 11)
      - Kudos, 2001 (Box 162, Folder 12)
      - Kudos, 2002 (Box 162, Folder 13)
      - Kudos, 2003 (Box 162, Folder 14)
      - Kudos, 2004 (Box 162, Folder 15)
      - Kudos, 2005 (Box 162, Folder 16)
      - Kudos, 2006 (Box 162, Folder 17)
    - Form Letters, 1985-2006
      This subseries contains form letter responses to constituents covering a wide array of topics. It is arranged alphabetically by topic.
      - Abortion, 1985-2004 (Box 163, Folder 1)
      - Aged, 1985-2004 (Box 163, Folder 2)
      - Agriculture, 1985-2005 (Box 163, Folder 3)
      - Animal Rights, 1985-1999 (Box 163, Folder 4)
      - Appropriations, 1985-2005 (Box 163, Folder 5)
      - Art, 1989-2005 (Box 163, Folder 6)
      - Arizona Issues, 1985-2006 (Box 163, Folder 7)
      - Banking/Finance (1 of 2), 1985-2006 (Box 163, Folder 8)
      - Banking/Finance (2 of 2), 1985-2006 (Box 163, Folder 9)
      - Budget (1 of 2), 1985-2005 (Box 163, Folder 10)
      - Budget (2 of 2), 1985-2005 (Box 163, Folder 11)
      - Business Industry (BU), 1987-2006 (Box 163, Folder 12)
      - Commemoratives (CV), 1990-2006 (Box 163, Folder 13)
      - Communication, 1986-2006 (Box 163, Folder 14)
      - Congress, 1985-1999 (Box 163, Folder 15)
      - Constitution, 1990-2002 (Box 163, Folder 16)
      - Customs, 1989-1993 (Box 163, Folder 17)
      - Defense (1 of 5), 1985-2006 (Box 163, Folder 18)
      - Defense (2 of 5), 1985-2006 (Box 163, Folder 19)
      - Defense (3 of 5), 1985-2006 (Box 163, Folder 20)
      - Defense (4 of 5), 1985-2006 (Box 164, Folder 1)
      - Defense (5 of 5), 1985-2006 (Box 164, Folder 2)
      - District of Columbia, 1989-1994 (Box 164, Folder 3)
      - Economy, 1985-1990 (Box 164, Folder 4)
      - Education (1 of 2), 1985-2006 (Box 164, Folder 5)
      - Education (2 of 2), 1985-2006 (Box 164, Folder 6)
      - Energy, 1985-2006 (Box 164, Folder 7)
      - Environment (1 of 7), 1985-2006 (Box 164, Folder 8)
      - Environment (2 of 7), 1985-2006 (Box 164, Folder 9)
      - Environment (3 of 7), 1985-2006 (Box 164, Folder 10)
      - Environment (4 of 7), 1985-2006 (Box 164, Folder 11)
      - Environment (5 of 7), 1985-2006 (Box 164, Folder 12)
      - Environment (6 of 7), 1985-2006 (Box 164, Folder 13)
      - Environment (7 of 7), 1985-2006 (Box 164, Folder 14)
      - Foreign Affairs (1 of 2), 1985-1998 (Box 164, Folder 15)
      - Foreign Affairs (2 of 2), 1985-1998 (Box 164, Folder 16)
      - Foreign Affairs, 1985-2005 (Box 165, Folder 1)
      - Fundraising Letters, 2001-2003 (Box 165, Folder 2)
      - Government and Civil Services, 1987-2002 (Box 165, Folder 3)
      - Health (1 of 6), 1985-2006 (Box 165, Folder 4)
      - Health (2 of 6), 1985-2006 (Box 165, Folder 5)
      - Health (3 of 6), 1985-2006 (Box 165, Folder 6)
      - Health (4 of 6), 1985-2006 (Box 165, Folder 7)
      - Health (5 of 6), 1985-2006 (Box 165, Folder 8)
      - Health (6 of 6), 1985-2006 (Box 165, Folder 9)
      - Housing, 1987-1995 (Box 165, Folder 10)
      - Indians, 1987-2003 (Box 165, Folder 11)
      - Immigration, 1987-1990 (Box 165, Folder 12)
      - Immigration, 1987-2005 (Box 165, Folder 13)
      - Judiciary (1 of 3), 1985-2006 (Box 165, Folder 14)
      - Judiciary (2 of 3), 1985-2006 (Box 165, Folder 15)
      - Judiciary (3 of 3), 1985-2006 (Box 166, Folder 1)
      - Labor, 1987-2002 (Box 166, Folder 2)
      - Mexico, 1990-2006 (Box 166, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous (1 of 9), 1987-2005 (Box 166, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous (2 of 9), 1987-2005 (Box 166, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous (3 of 9), 1987-2005 (Box 166, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous (4 of 9), 1987-2005 (Box 166, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous (5 of 9), 1987-2005 (Box 166, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous (6 of 9), 1987-2005 (Box 166, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous (7 of 9), 1987-2005 (Box 166, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous (8 of 9), 1987-2005 (Box 166, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous (9 of 9), 1987-2005 (Box 166, Folder 12)
      - Postal, 1985-1999 (Box 166, Folder 13)
      - Science/Space, 1990-2004 (Box 166, Folder 14)
      - Social Security, 1985-1995 (Box 166, Folder 15)
      - Social Services, 1985-2002 (Box 166, Folder 16)
      - Taxes (1 of 3), 1985-2006 (Box 167, Folder 1)
      - Taxes (2 of 3), 1985-2006 (Box 167, Folder 2)
      - Taxes (3 of 3), 1985-2006 (Box 167, Folder 3)
      - Trade, 1985-2006 (Box 167, Folder 4)
      - Transportation, 1985-2006 (Box 167, Folder 5)
      - Veterans (1 of 4), 1988-2006 (Box 167, Folder 6)
      - Veterans (2 of 4), 1988-2006 (Box 167, Folder 7)
      - Veterans (3 of 4), 1988-2006 (Box 167, Folder 8)
      - Veterans (4 of 4), 1988-2006 (Box 167, Folder 9)
    - Mail with Officials, 1985-2006
      This subseries contains letters from a variety of government officials as well as signature files. It is arranged alphabetically.
      - Bush, George H.W., 1989-1991 (Box 167, Folder 10)
      - Bush, George H.W., 2002-2006 (Box 167, Folder 11)
      - Cheney, Dick, 1989-1990 (Box 167, Folder 12)
      - Clinton, Bill, 1993-2001 (Box 167, Folder 13)
      - DeConcini, Dennis, 1986 (Box 167, Folder 14)
      - Ford, Gerald R., 1987 (Box 167, Folder 15)
      - General, A-W, 1985 (Box 167, Folder 16)
      - General, 1986 (Box 167, Folder 17)
      - General, A-V, 1986 (Box 167, Folder 18)
      - General, A-Z, 1987 (Box 167, Folder 19)
      - General, A-W, 1988 (Box 167, Folder 20)
      - General, A-W, 1989 (Box 168, Folder 1)
      - General, A-Y, 1990 (Box 168, Folder 2)
      - General, A-S, 1991 (Box 168, Folder 3)
      - General, A-V, 1992 (Box 168, Folder 4)
      - General, A-W, 1993-1994 (Box 168, Folder 5)
      - General, 1994 (Box 168, Folder 6)
      - General, C-R, 1995 (Box 168, Folder 7)
      - General, A-X, 1995-1997 (Box 168, Folder 8)
      - General, A-S, 1998 (Box 168, Folder 9)
      - General, A-T, 1999 (Box 168, Folder 10)
      - General, B-W, 2000 (Box 168, Folder 11)
      - General, B-Y, 2001 (Box 168, Folder 12)
      - General, A-R, 2002 (Box 168, Folder 13)
      - General, B-Y, 2003 (Box 168, Folder 14)
      - General, A-W, 2004-2005 (Box 168, Folder 15)
      - General, B-T, 2006 (Box 168, Folder 16)
      - Goldwater, Barry, 1992 (Box 168, Folder 17)
      - Gore, Al, 1997-1998 (Box 168, Folder 18)
      - King, Coretta Scott, 1988 (Box 168, Folder 19)
      - Napolitano, Janet, 2003-2006 (Box 168, Folder 20)
      - Reagan, Ronald, 1985-1988 (Box 168, Folder 21)
      - Thatcher, Margaret, 1986 (Box 168, Folder 22)
      - Signature files, 1985 (Box 168, Folder 23)
      - Signature files (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 168, Folder 24)
      - Signature files (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 168, Folder 25)
      - Signature files, 1987 (Box 168, Folder 26)
      - Signature files, 1988 (Box 168, Folder 27)
      - Signature files, 1989 (Box 169, Folder 1)
      - Signature files, 1990 (Box 169, Folder 2)
      - Signature files (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 169, Folder 3)
      - Signature files (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 169, Folder 4)
      - Signature files, 1992 (Box 169, Folder 5)
      - Signature files (1 of 3), 1993 (Box 169, Folder 6)
      - Signature files (2 of 3), 1993 (Box 169, Folder 7)
      - Signature files (3 of 3), 1993 (Box 169, Folder 8)
      - Signature files (1 of 3), 1994 (Box 169, Folder 9)
      - Signature files (2 of 3), 1994 (Box 169, Folder 10)
      - Signature files (3 of 3), 1994 (Box 169, Folder 11)
      - Signature files, 1997 (Box 169, Folder 12)
      - Signature files (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 169, Folder 13)
      - Signature files (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 169, Folder 14)
      - Signature files (1 of 3), 1999 (Box 169, Folder 15)
      - Signature files (2 of 3), 1999 (Box 169, Folder 16)
      - Signature files (3 of 3), 1999 (Box 170, Folder 1)
      - Signature files, 2000 (Box 170, Folder 2)
      - Signature files (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 170, Folder 3)
      - Signature files (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 170, Folder 4)
      - Signature files (1 of 3), 2002 (Box 170, Folder 5)
      - Signature files (2 of 3), 2002 (Box 170, Folder 6)
      - Signature files (3 of 3), 2002 (Box 170, Folder 7)
      - Signature files, 2003 (Box 170, Folder 8)
      - Signature folder, 1st Session (1 of 2), 2003 (Box 170, Folder 9)
      - Signature folder, 1st Session (2 of 2), 2003 (Box 170, Folder 10)
      - Signature folder, 2nd Session (1 of 2), 2004 (Box 170, Folder 11)
      - Signature folder, 2nd Session (2 of 2), 2004 (Box 170, Folder 12)
      - Udall, Morris, 1985-1986 (Box 170, Folder 13)
    - Constituent Mail, 1985-2006
      This subseries contains correspondence by year from constituents. It is arranged alphabetically.
      - Letters, A-W, 1985 (Box 171, Folder 1)
      - Letters, B-Z, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 2)
      - Letters, A-B, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 3)
      - Letters, C-F, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 4)
      - Letters, G-H, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 5)
      - Letters, J-K, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 6)
      - Letters, L-M, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 7)
      - Letters, N-Q, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 8)
      - Letters, R-T, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 9)
      - Letters, V-Y, 1987 (Box 171, Folder 10)
      - Letters, A-B, 1988 (Box 172, Folder 1)
      - Letters, C-D, 1988 (Box 172, Folder 2)
      - Letters, E-F, 1988 (Box 172, Folder 3)
      - Letters, G-H, 1988 (Box 172, Folder 4)
      - Letters, J-L, 1988 (Box 172, Folder 5)
      - Letters, M-N, 1988 (Box 172, Folder 6)
      - Letters, O-Q, 1988 (Box 172, Folder 7)
      - Letters, R-S, 1988 (Box 172, Folder 8)
      - Letters, T-Z, 1988 (Box 172, Folder 9)
      - Letters, A-L, 1989 (Box 172, Folder 10)
      - Letters, M-W, 1989 (Box 172, Folder 11)
      - Letters, A-U, 1990 (Box 173, Folder 1)
      - Letters, A-Y, 1991 (Box 173, Folder 2)
      - Letters, A-T (1 of 2), 1992 (Box 173, Folder 3)
      - Letters, A-T (2 of 2), 1992 (Box 173, Folder 4)
      - Letters, B-S, 1993 (Box 173, Folder 5)
      - Letters, A-Z, 1994 (Box 173, Folder 6)
      - Letters, B-R, 1995 (Box 173, Folder 7)
      - Letters, A-F, 1996 (Box 173, Folder 8)
      - Letters, G-L, 1996 (Box 173, Folder 9)
      - Letters, M-R, 1996 (Box 173, Folder 10)
      - Letters, S-Z, 1996 (Box 173, Folder 11)
      - Letters, 1997 (Box 173, Folder 12)
      - Letters, B-Y, 1998 (Box 173, Folder 13)
      - Letters, A-Y, 1999 (Box 173, Folder 14)
      - Letters, A-W, 2000 (Box 173, Folder 15)
      - Letters, A-W, 2001 (Box 173, Folder 16)
      - Letters, A-W, 2002 (Box 173, Folder 17)
      - Letters, C-W, 2003 (Box 173, Folder 18)
      - Letters, A-L, 2004 (Box 174, Folder 1)
      - Letters, M-Z, 2004 (Box 174, Folder 2)
      - Letters, A-R, 2005 (Box 174, Folder 3)
      - Letters, A-R, 2006 (Box 174, Folder 4)
      - Letters, M, 2006 (Box 174, Folder 5)
      - Letters, N-Z, 2006 (Box 174, Folder 6)
      - Letters, S-Z, 2006 (Box 174, Folder 7)
      - Opinion Forms, 1986 (Box 174, Folder 8)
      - Opinion Forms, 1987 (Box 174, Folder 9)
      - Opinion Forms, 1988 (Box 174, Folder 10)
      - Opinion Forms, 1990 (Box 174, Folder 11)
      - Opinion Forms, 1994 (Box 174, Folder 12)
      - Opinion Forms, 1996 (Box 174, Folder 13)
      - Opinion Forms, 2002 (Box 174, Folder 14)
      - Opinion Forms, 2003 (Box 174, Folder 15)
      - Opinion Forms, 2004 (Box 174, Folder 16)
      - Opinion Forms (1 of 3), 2005 (Box 174, Folder 17)
      - Opinion Forms (2 of 3), 2005 (Box 174, Folder 18)
      - Opinion Forms (3 of 3), 2005 (Box 174, Folder 19)
      - Opinion Forms, 2006 (Box 174, Folder 20)
      - Opinion Forms, undated (Box 174, Folder 21)
  - Series 7: Press Files, 1985-2006
    This series contains press clippings, press releases, media kits and franked mail.
    - Articles by Kolbe, 1985-1989 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Articles by Kolbe, 1990 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Articles by Kolbe, 1994-2004 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Articles by Kolbe, 2005-2006 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Congressional Art Contest, 1989-1997 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Franked mail, 1991-2002 (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Franked mail, 2004-2006 (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - The Jim Kolbe Show, 2005 (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - Kolbe-Boyd Social Security Bill press packet, 2005 (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - Media requests, 1991 (Box 175, Folder 10)
    - Media requests (1 of 2), 2005-2006 (Box 175, Folder 11)
    - Media requests (2 of 2), 2005-2006 (Box 175, Folder 12)
    - Press clippings, 1987-1990 (Box 175, Folder 13)
    - Press clippings (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 175, Folder 14)
    - Press clippings (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 175, Folder 15)
    - Press clippings (1 of 3), 1992 (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings (2 of 3), 1992 (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings (3 of 3), 1992 (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings (2 of 2), 1993 (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings (1 of 21), 1994 (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings (2 of 21), 1994 (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings (3 of 21), 1994 (Box 176, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings (4 of 21), 1994 (Box 176, Folder 9)
    - Press clippings (5 of 21), 1994 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings (6 of 21), 1994 (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings (7 of 21), 1994 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings (8 of 21), 1994 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings (9 of 21), 1994 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings (10 of 21), 1994 (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings (11 of 21), 1994 (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings (12 of 21), 1994 (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings (13 of 21), 1994 (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - Press clippings (14 of 21), 1994 (Box 177, Folder 10)
    - Press clippings (15 of 21), 1994 (Box 177, Folder 11)
    - Press clippings (16 of 21), 1994 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings (17 of 21), 1994 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings (18 of 21), 1994 (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings (19 of 21), 1994 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings (20 of 21), 1994 (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings (21 of 21), 1994 (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings, 1995 (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - Press clippings (1 of 11), 1997 (Box 178, Folder 10)
    - Press clippings (2 of 11), 1997 (Box 178, Folder 11)
    - Press clippings (3 of 11), 1997 (Box 178, Folder 12)
    - Press clippings (4 of 11), 1997 (Box 178, Folder 13)
    - Press clippings (5 of 11), 1997 (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings (6 of 11), 1997 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings (7 of 11), 1997 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings (8 of 11), 1997 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings (9 of 11), 1997 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings (10 of 11), 1997 (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings (11 of 11), 1997 (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings (1 of 13), 1998 (Box 179, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings (2 of 13), 1998 (Box 179, Folder 9)
    - Press clippings (3 of 13), 1998 (Box 179, Folder 10)
    - Press clippings (4 of 13), 1998 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings (5 of 13), 1998 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings (6 of 13), 1998 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings (7 of 13), 1998 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings (8 of 13), 1998 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings (9 of 13), 1998 (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings (10 of 13), 1998 (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings (11 of 13), 1998 (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings (12 of 13), 1998 (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - Press clippings (13 of 13), 1998 (Box 180, Folder 10)
    - Press clippings (1 of 7), 1999 (Box 180, Folder 11)
    - Press clippings (2 of 7), 1999 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings (3 of 7), 1999 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings (4 of 7), 1999 (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings (5 of 7), 1999 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings (6 of 7), 1999 (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings (7 of 7), 1999 (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings (1 of 12), 2000 (Box 181, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings (2 of 12), 2000 (Box 181, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings (3 of 12), 2000 (Box 181, Folder 9)
    - Press clippings (4 of 12), 2000 (Box 181, Folder 10)
    - Press clippings (5 of 12), 2000 (Box 181, Folder 11)
    - Press clippings (6 of 12), 2000 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings (7 of 12), 2000 (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings (8 of 12), 2000 (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings (9 of 12), 2000 (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings (10 of 12), 2000 (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings (11 of 12), 2000 (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings (12 of 12), 2000 (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings, 2001 (Box 182, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings, 2002-2004 (Box 182, Folder 9)
    - Press clippings (1 of 8), 2005 (Box 182, Folder 10)
    - Press clippings (2 of 8), 2005 (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings (3 of 8), 2005 (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings (4 of 8), 2005 (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings (5 of 8), 2005 (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings (6 of 8), 2005 (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings (7 of 8), 2005 (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings (8 of 8), 2005 (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings (1 of 2), 2006 (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings (2 of 2), 2006 (Box 183, Folder 9)
    - Press clippings- Border, 2002 (Box 183, Folder 10)
    - Press clippings- Border security (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 183, Folder 11)
    - Press clippings- Border security (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 183, Folder 12)
    - Press clippings- Defense Base Closure and Realignment Commission, 2005 (Box 183, Folder 13)
    - Press clippings- Election, 2005 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings- Foreign Operations, 2005 (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings- Hurricane Katrina, 2005 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings- One Dollar Coin (1 of 2), 1987-1995 (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings- One Dollar Coin (2 of 2), 1987-1995 (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings- Outing, 1996 (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings- Republican National Convention, 2000 (Box 184, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings- Social Security, 1999 (Box 184, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings- Social Security (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 184, Folder 9)
    - Press clippings- Social Security (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 184, Folder 10)
    - Press clippings- Trade, 1996-1999 (Box 184, Folder 11)
    - Press plans, 1986-1991 (Box 184, Folder 12)
    - Press releases, 1985 (Box 184, Folder 13)
    - Pres releases, 1987-1989 (Box 184, Folder 14)
    - Press releases (1 of 3), 1990-1991 (Box 184, Folder 15)
    - Press releases (2 of 3), 1990-1991 (Box 184, Folder 16)
    - Press releases (3 of 3), 1990-1991 (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Press releases, 1992 (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - Press releases (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - Press releases (2 of 2), 1993 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Press releases, 1994-1995 (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - Press releases, 1996 (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Press releases, 1997-2000 (Box 185, Folder 7)
    - Press releases, 2001-2002 (Box 185, Folder 8)
    - Press releases, 2003 (Box 185, Folder 9)
    - Press releases, 2004-2006 (Box 185, Folder 10)
    - Scripts, 1999 (Box 185, Folder 11)
  - Series 8: Subject Files, 1980-2006
    This series contains subject files related to specific topics researched by Kolbe’s congressional staff which includes news and press clippings and other related materials. Also included are news clippings and reference materials for speeches. It is arranged alphabetically by topic.
    - Adoption, 1996-2001 (Box 185, Folder 12)
    - Abortion, 1987 (Box 185, Folder 13)
    - Air Services, 1989 (Box 185, Folder 14)
    - Apache Junction, 1990 (Box 185, Folder 15)
    - Apache Junction Community School Archaeological Dig, 1989 (Box 185, Folder 16)
    - Arivaca Creek Acquisition, 1989 (Box 185, Folder 17)
    - Arizona Cities (1 of 2), 1985-2006 (Box 185, Folder 18)
    - Arizona Cities (2 of 2), 1985-2006 (Box 185, Folder 19)
    - Arizona Health Care Cost Containment System (1 of 2), 1994-1998 (Box 185, Folder 20)
    - Arizona Health Care Cost Containment System (2 of 2), 1994-1998 (Box 185, Folder 21)
    - Arizona-Mexico Commission, 1991-2005 (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Asbestos, 2004-2005 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Arizona English, 1987-1988 (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Bicentennial of the United States Constitution (1 of 5), 1986-1988 (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Bicentennial of the United States Constitution (2 of 5), 1986-1988 (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - Bicentennial of the United States Constitution (3 of 5), 1986-1988 (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - Bicentennial of the United States Constitution (4 of 5), 1986-1988 (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - Bicentennial of the United States Constitution (5 of 5), 1986-1988 (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - Biz and Associates/Casa Grande, 1989 (Box 186, Folder 9)
    - Bureau of Land Management Land Exchanges (1 of 2), 1992-1996 (Box 186, Folder 10)
    - Bureau of Land Management Land Exchanges (2 of 2), 1992-1996 (Box 186, Folder 11)
    - Border crime, 1993 (Box 186, Folder 12)
    - Border fees, 1995 (Box 186, Folder 13)
    - Border fence, 1993 (Box 186, Folder 14)
    - Border infrastructure, 1993-2005 (Box 186, Folder 15)
    - Border issues (1 of 2), 1993-2003 (Box 186, Folder 16)
    - Border issues (2 of 2), 1993-2003 (Box 186, Folder 17)
    - Border patrol, 1995-1996 (Box 186, Folder 18)
    - Border patrol, 2001 (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Budget and The Deficit, 1985-1988 (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Business, 1997 (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - Cactus Ferruginous Pygmy Owl (1 of 2), 1995-1997 (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - Cactus Ferruginous Pygmy Owl (2 of 2), 1995-1997 (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - Cactus Ferruginous Pygmy Owl (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - Cactus Ferruginous Pygmy Owl (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - Cactus Ferruginous Pygmy Owl, 1999 (Box 187, Folder 8)
    - Calabasas, 1990 (Box 187, Folder 9)
    - Cananca Border Crossing, 1990-1991 (Box 187, Folder 10)
    - Casa Grande, 1989-1990 (Box 187, Folder 11)
    - Caterpillar Incorporated, 1989 (Box 187, Folder 12)
    - Census, 1988-1990 (Box 187, Folder 13)
    - Center for Disease Control Flu-Vaccine, 2000 (Box 187, Folder 14)
    - Central Arizona Project Flooding, Marana, Arizona, 1987-1990 (Box 187, Folder 15)
    - Child Care, 1989 (Box 187, Folder 16)
    - Chinese Students, 1989 (Box 187, Folder 17)
    - Clinton Impeachment, 1998 (Box 187, Folder 18)
    - Clippings, 1992-1995 (Box 187, Folder 19)
    - Clippings, 1997 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Clippings (1 of 10), 1998 (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - Clippings (2 of 10), 1998 (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - Clippings (3 of 10), 1998 (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - Clippings (4 of 10), 1998 (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - Clippings (5 of 10), 1998 (Box 188, Folder 6)